usask.ca 2011-12-31

# Privacy - University of Saskatchewan

The University of Saskatchewan is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of personal information. All personal information that is collected by the University of Saskatchewan, whether through this website (www.usask.ca) or by other means, is managed according to the Saskatchewan Local Authority Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act and the University’s Data Management, Data Access and Data Use policy.

## Automatic Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

University of Saskatchewan web servers automatically collect and store the following information from its websites:

  * The Internet Protocol (IP) Address and domain name used for the computer accessing the website.
  * The type of browser and operating system;
  * The date and time of the visit and;
  * The web pages or services accessed.

Information collected automatically is maintained in a secure environment. Summary reports will be used for purposes such as assessing system performance, improving web services and website management. As per the data use policy, the University will not use this data for other purposes, unless required to do so as part of an internal investigation or other law enforcement purpose.

Some University of Saskatchewan websites may distribute a small file to your browser, called a "cookie". Such files allow us to provide you with personalized information on your future visits to our websites; they are not used for any other purpose. If you wish, you may change the settings on your web browser to deny cookies or to warn you when cookies will be deposited. 

In order to improve website performance and user experience, some University of Saskatchewan websites use a third party web analytics service that stores information outside of Canada where it may not receive the same privacy protection it receives in Canada. Summary reports will be used to improve usability on our sites and to help support the online needs of visitors. 

## Information Provided Voluntarily in E-mail and Web Forms

Some personal information, including but not limited to name and e-mail address, may be provided voluntarily by users of University of Saskatchewan websites to request services such as newsletter sign up, image download, online surveys and other similar services.

Personal information provided voluntarily in an e-mail or by filling out a form will be used only for internal purposes such as responding to your message. This information may also be shared with our customer service representatives, Webmaster, Web Administrator or other employees as a means to continually improve customer service.

## Links to Third Party Sites

University of Saskatchewan websites contain links to other sites. While the University of Saskatchewan endeavours to link to other sites that have similar high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other sites.

## More Information 

Questions or concerns regarding our management of this privacy statement may be directed to:

Rayelle Johnston, LL.B.  
Access and Privacy Officer  
E211 - 105 Administration Place  
Phone: (306) 966-8596  
E-mail: [rayelle.johnston@usask.ca](mailto:rayelle.johnston@usask.ca)
